<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.vcque.prompto</id>
    <name>Prompto - ChatGPT Assistant</name>
    <vendor email="vocquet.ocquet@gmail.com" url="https://github.com/vcque">Vincent Ocquet</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
      <h1>A coding assistant based on ChatGPT.</h1>
      <br>
      <p>
        The core concept of Prompto is to capture your IDE state in order to contextualize queries you send to ChatGPT. <br>
        This allows the generated responses to be fine-tuned to your use-case, building on the code present in your project. <br>
        Prompto has been mainly used and tested on Java and Typescript projects but can also work on other languages in a limited way.
      </p>
      <br>
      <p>
        <strong>be mindful of potential issues with private or sensitive data</strong>. You can preview the context data before sending your prompt to the LLM.
      </p>
      <br>
      <p>
        To use it, fill in your API key in Prompto settings and press Alt-Enter in the editor to be presented with prompto actions.
      </p>
      <br>
      <h2>General use</h2>
      <p>
        Starting a Prompto action opens a dialog which shows which context information to add to your prompt.
        You can then either send the query to the LLM or export it to your clipboard.
      </p>
      <h2>Prompto implement</h2>
      <p>
        Use this action on an existing method to implement or modify it. <br>
        Prompto will use the relevant type definitions of your project to build an optimal implementation. <br>
        This is best used on code like converter methods, test cases or usage of external (and well-known) libraries. <br>
        This is a Java only feature.
      </p>
      <h2>Prompto ask</h2>
      <p>
        Use this action to ask a quick question about your project. <br>
        This can be useful to get a answer that you know will be short and mostly accurate.
        If you have doubts, it is better to export it to clipboard and start a chat with the LLM of your choice instead.
      </p>
      <h2>Prompto sql - Intellij Ultimate only</h2>
      <p>
        In a database console, ask Prompto to generate a SQL script. <br>
        Prompto will have access to your database schema to generate a relevant SQL query. <br>
        Note that this feature currently only works for small databases. (~40 tables max)
      </p>
      <br>
      <p>Feedback is welcome at <a href="https://github.com/vcque/prompto">https://github.com/vcque/prompto</a>. Have fun!</p>
    ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <h1>0.9.0</h1>
        <h2>New Features</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Typescript support: allow `Prompto implement` on TS functions</li>
          <li>Typescript support: add TS type definition to prompto scope</li>
          <li>UI: set clipboard as default quick action when the API key is not set</li>
          <li>Use tabs instead of spaces to save token usage</li>
          <li>Sql database schema is available to Prompto ask</li>
          <li>Allow the plugin to be extended to add more type of data to the prompt scope</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>Bug Fixes</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Small prompt enhancements</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>
    <depends>org.intellij.plugins.markdown</depends>
    <depends optional="true" config-file="prompto-withDatabase.xml">com.intellij.database</depends>
    <depends optional="true" config-file="prompto-withJavascript.xml">JavaScript</depends>
    <extensionPoints>
        <extensionPoint name="promptoRetriever" interface="com.vcque.prompto.contexts.PromptoRetriever"/>
    </extensionPoints>
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <applicationConfigurable parentId="tools" instance="com.vcque.prompto.settings.PromptoSettingsConfigurable"
                                 id="com.vcque.prompto.settings.PromptoSettingsConfigurable"
                                 displayName="Prompto Settings"/>
        <applicationService serviceImplementation="com.vcque.prompto.settings.PromptoSettingsState"/>
        <notificationGroup id="Prompto"
                           displayType="BALLOON"
        />
        <intentionAction>
            <className>com.vcque.prompto.actions.PromptoImplementAction</className>
            <category>Prompto</category>
        </intentionAction>
        <intentionAction>
            <className>com.vcque.prompto.actions.PromptoAskAction</className>
            <category>Prompto</category>
        </intentionAction>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>