<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.vcque.prompto</id>
    <name>Prompto</name>
    <vendor email="vocquet.ocquet@gmail.com" url="https://github.com/vcque">Vincent Ocquet</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>A coding assistant based on ChatGPT 3.5.</p>
      <br>
      <p>
        This plugin provides actions that capture your current editor's state to contextualize the prompt you send to ChatGPT. <br>
        Each action lists the context sent so that you can <strong>be mindful of potential issues with private or sensitive data</strong>.
      </p>
      <br>
      <p>
        To use it, fill in your API key in Prompto settings and press Alt-Enter in the editor to be presented with the following Prompto actions:
        <ul>
        <li>prompto <strong>ask</strong>: asks a simple question about the visualized code.</li>
        <li>prompto <strong>rewrite method</strong>: rewrites the current method based on your input (e.g., add documentation or fix this issue).</li>
        <li>prompto <strong>raw insert</strong>: generates anything based on your input and inserts it at your current caret location.</li>
        <li>prompto <strong>clipboard</strong>: captures your editor's state, builds a Prompto prompt, and saves it to your clipboard so that you can use it in the ChatGPT web app.</li>
        </ul>
      </p>
      <p>
        Here are some tips and use-cases:
        <ul>
        <li>If you don't have an API key, you can still use the Prompto clipboard and paste it in the ChatGPT web app.</li>
        <li>Prompto answers often lack accuracy, and you will have to proof-check them. However, it still provides an amazing starting point to iterate upon.</li>
        <li>Prompto is best used for simple but lengthy tasks such as: writing documentation, unit tests, mock datasets, converter methods, etc.</li>
        <li>Prompto has more knowledge about well-known cases and technologies than niche ones.</li>
        <li>Prompto's attention span is limited and will provide better answers for short or medium files and might outright fail for large ones.</li>
        </ul>
      </p>

      <p>Feedback is welcome at <a href="https://github.com/vcque/prompto">https://github.com/vcque/prompto</a>. Have fun!</p>
    ]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <applicationConfigurable parentId="tools" instance="com.vcque.prompto.settings.PromptoSettingsConfigurable"
                                 id="com.vcque.prompto.settings.PromptoSettingsConfigurable"
                                 displayName="Prompto Settings"/>
        <applicationService serviceImplementation="com.vcque.prompto.settings.PromptoSettingsState"/>
        <notificationGroup id="Prompto"
                           displayType="BALLOON"
        />
        <intentionAction>
            <className>com.vcque.prompto.actions.PromptoClipboardAction</className>
            <category>Prompto</category>
        </intentionAction>
        <intentionAction>
            <className>com.vcque.prompto.actions.PromptoRewriteMethodAction</className>
            <category>Prompto</category>
        </intentionAction>
        <intentionAction>
            <className>com.vcque.prompto.actions.PromptoAskAction</className>
            <category>Prompto</category>
        </intentionAction>
        <intentionAction>
            <className>com.vcque.prompto.actions.PromptoRawInsertAction</className>
            <category>Prompto</category>
        </intentionAction>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>